<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on r-log</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content in Home on r-log</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Getting Started with Hugo</title><link>/coding/getting-started-with-hugo/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>/coding/getting-started-with-hugo/</guid><description>Hugo is a fast and modern static site generator written in Go. It&amp;rsquo;s designed to make website creation fun again.
Why Hugo? Hugo is one of the most popular open-source static site generators. With its amazing speed and flexibility, Hugo makes building websites fun again. Here are some key benefits:
Speed: Hugo is incredibly fast, building sites in milliseconds Flexibility: Supports multiple content types and taxonomies No Dependencies: Single binary with no runtime dependencies Live Reload: See changes instantly while developing Basic Setup To get started with Hugo, you need to:</description></item><item><title>The Art of Blogging</title><link>/writing/the-art-of-blogging/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 15:30:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>/writing/the-art-of-blogging/</guid><description>Blogging is more than just writing—it&amp;rsquo;s about sharing ideas, connecting with readers, and creating value through content.
Finding Your Voice Every blogger has a unique perspective. The key is to:
Write authentically Share your genuine experiences Be consistent in your tone Connect with your audience Content That Matters Great blog posts solve problems or provide insights. Focus on:
Value: What will readers gain from this post? Clarity: Is your message clear and concise?</description></item><item><title>Discovering New Sounds</title><link>/music/discovering-new-sounds/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>/music/discovering-new-sounds/</guid><description>Music discovery is an endless journey. In the age of streaming, we have access to more music than ever before, yet finding those hidden gems remains a delightful challenge.
The Joy of Discovery There&amp;rsquo;s something magical about stumbling upon a song that speaks to you. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s:
A random playlist suggestion A friend&amp;rsquo;s recommendation Background music in a coffee shop An opening act at a concert Each discovery adds to your personal soundtrack.</description></item><item><title>Remote Work Lessons</title><link>/careers/remote-work-lessons/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>/careers/remote-work-lessons/</guid><description>After years of remote work, I&amp;rsquo;ve learned valuable lessons about productivity, balance, and staying connected in a distributed environment.
Setting Boundaries Working from home blurs the line between personal and professional life. Key strategies:
Dedicated workspace: Even if it&amp;rsquo;s just a corner of a room Set hours: Start and stop at consistent times Communicate availability: Let colleagues know when you&amp;rsquo;re working Take real breaks: Step away from the screen regularly Staying Productive Remote productivity requires intentionality:</description></item><item><title>Post 3</title><link>/posts/post-3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 11:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>/posts/post-3/</guid><description>Occaecat aliqua consequat laborum ut ex aute aliqua culpa quis irure esse magna dolore quis. Proident fugiat labore eu laboris officia Lorem enim. Ipsum occaecat cillum ut tempor id sint aliqua incididunt nisi incididunt reprehenderit. Voluptate ad minim sint est aute aliquip esse occaecat tempor officia qui sunt. Aute ex ipsum id ut in est velit est laborum incididunt. Aliqua qui id do esse sunt eiusmod id deserunt eu nostrud aute sit ipsum.</description></item><item><title>Post 2</title><link>/posts/post-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>/posts/post-2/</guid><description>Anim eiusmod irure incididunt sint cupidatat. Incididunt irure irure irure nisi ipsum do ut quis fugiat consectetur proident cupidatat incididunt cillum. Dolore voluptate occaecat qui mollit laborum ullamco et. Ipsum laboris officia anim laboris culpa eiusmod ex magna ex cupidatat anim ipsum aute. Mollit aliquip occaecat qui sunt velit ut cupidatat reprehenderit enim sunt laborum. Velit veniam in officia nulla adipisicing ut duis officia.
Exercitation voluptate irure in irure tempor mollit Lorem nostrud ad officia.</description></item><item><title>Post 1</title><link>/posts/post-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>/posts/post-1/</guid><description>Tempor proident minim aliquip reprehenderit dolor et ad anim Lorem duis sint eiusmod. Labore ut ea duis dolor. Incididunt consectetur proident qui occaecat incididunt do nisi Lorem. Tempor do laborum elit laboris excepteur eiusmod do. Eiusmod nisi excepteur ut amet pariatur adipisicing Lorem.
Occaecat nulla excepteur dolore excepteur duis eiusmod ullamco officia anim in voluptate ea occaecat officia. Cillum sint esse velit ea officia minim fugiat. Elit ea esse id aliquip pariatur cupidatat id duis minim incididunt ea ea.</description></item></channel></rss>